in celery college school, stocks will
go into inverted positions and
we will see if this can beat, so
let's start, first of all, if you have seen
it a little more, finally, there is a
little profit on Bigg Boss and
here and like and
if seen here, we are going to subscribe a
little more from the market,
before that if we talk about it, then the soil is near its
golden brother
20180 black here
and finally we
can see its first support of 1768 sinking in it, so
like if the selection continues here
and we complete the crucial support of 17500, then only
after this
we will be able to place any sale in it on a positional basis
and MS Word is their one and a half, so
here the open interest which shows that
next it shows us the
fixed setting here at 1762 and
that too because Services, if the
market here sweats below 1768 on Monday,
then you will get a price of 1768  In Manipur
contact cooking gas, if it appeals to 750, then
in that case you
can add your profit to it and if you
want to fold it, then you have to go by placing your stop loss.
If we
talk about it here at this time, then the bank team first does
its work by going up by 10,
but later you can use it, like
we saw a dip in it, but later we used to go
daily, another one can be seen sometimes in it,
so guys, if we look at it now,
we have to make a fold in it only after 37822,
otherwise this fit can
go up further due to amendments, so
you have to print your trademark behind it.
If we look at the status, then the open
interest, which is there, shows
that the higher levels are at 3822 and
above 130, which one is tight right now, so if
you take any cigarette, then
comment a little and if possible, you can do
your trading here on the basis of price action.
If it
breaks 3770, then you should buy a little more in the side here from inside
and you
can acquire options contract here at 3804.
Let's look at that system in which
we
first of all, because this in
itself
increases the chances of making profit in this,
if
you buy a
little more in this,
because here the next support is
above 20, here
in the bring to front, on the basis of association,
more than 60 shares, then the
bank is a little here that
after a consolidation, the stock which came up a little, the
formation of Diya Pot pattern which happened on the same day is seen, so
guys, if Ritesh does his examination of section 125 from this fit, then we can
see a break in it in the future
because on its break, then the next
support will be seen, or the
career crib of 120 260, right now if 285 is broken, we can
see at least 528 in it once,
so  Based on that, we will take
our profit below 280. The
next stock after this is
Bhabhi and this stock is also in a bearish trend
because a
recent Burfi pattern can be seen here. So, guys,
if we open here below 28,
which was its previous question on the
material of these two, the talk was a little accurate between October. So, guys, if
you break 220 here,
you can see the lovers till 2018 on Monday.
After this, the final stock is Transport
and in this too, which was seen on the off side for the last few years,
due to B 310 Dual SIM, we can
see some profit in it in the future.
Here, the stock
consolidates and accepts feedback and if
a member comes here, then you can see at least this
Mithu achieve a target of ₹50 in the style plate. So,
guys, that  On this basis we will make our profit
and if the output goes below 54355
in the stock then you will have to place your stoploss further and
take your profit. That's all for today's video.
If you have not yet joined our Telegram channel then
definitely share it.
You will find the link and details in the description below.
And mode switch gear which cat
future and option can apply. By
default you can get our
building membership link and details
in the description below for Nifty updates. We will meet
in the next video. Till then
subscribe to the channel and if you
like the video then you
can like and share it as much as possible. So
thank you so much and is now in Excel
Jhal
Ki A
[Music]